Unit 18 Lesson 35
第十八单元  第三十五课
Men can cook, too!
男人也能做饭
Let's cook dinner, Robert.
我们来做饭吧  罗伯特
You can help me.
你来帮我忙吧
Give me some rice, please.
给我点米
There's some rice in that jar.
米在那个罐子里
Put some water in the pan,
在平底锅里放点水
and pass me a knife, please.
然后把刀递给我
Which one?
哪把刀
That one on the table.
桌子上的那把
OK, Dad. Here it is.
好的  爸爸  给你
Chop two onions, please.
切两个洋葱
OK, Dad. Chop two onions...
好的  爸爸  切两个洋葱
Is there a big spoon over there?
那边有个大勺子吗
Yes, Dad.
是的  爸爸
Pass me the big spoon, please.
把那个大勺子给我
I can't get a spoon.
爸爸  我不能又拿勺子
and chop an onion, Dad!
又切洋葱
You're right.
说的对
What about some plates?
那边有盘子吗
Dad, there are some plates on the shelf.
爸爸  架子上有盘子
There are some knives,
抽屉里还有刀叉
some forks and some spoons in the drawer.
和汤匙
And my hands are wet.
我的手湿了
You see, Robert,
你看  罗伯特
men can cook, too.
男人也可以做饭
Perhaps we can open a restaurant!
也许我们可以开家饭馆
Oh, yeah!
哦  是的